我们这是在哪儿?
Guys... where are we?
我在沙滩上找到了一条金属线
I found the wire on the beach.
我以为这和我们用信号接收器收到的
I thought it might have something to do with the transmission we picked up.
一个法国女人重复说了16年的话  会有点关系
with a Frenchwoman repeating on a loop for 16 years.
真的有这么久了么?
Has it really been that long?
是你
You.
你们的人...
Your people,
那些你决定了要回到他们那儿去的人...
the ones you're determined to get back to.
看紧他们
I'm alone now. Watch them closely.
我正在睡觉  一下子惊醒了  他正打算伤害我的孩子
On the island alone. I mean, I was sleeping, and I woke up,
我们必须弄清楚每个人是谁
We gotta find out who everyone is.
你想弄个人口普查?
Wanna start a census?
我问了在沙滩上的每一个人
I interviewed everyone at the beach.
Jack
其中一个不在旅客名单上
One of them isn't in the manifest.
他不是我们飞机上的人
He wasn't on the plane.
我们不是这个岛上唯一的一群人
We're not the only people on this island,
他们攻击我们  妨害我们  绑架我们  谋杀我们
They've attacked us! Sabotaged us, abducted us, murdered us.
也许是时候该考虑一下怎么去对付他们了
Maybe it's time we started worrying about them.
Danielle?
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
当我看见黑烟的时候
When I saw black smoke...
你们只有3个选择...
You have only three choices.
我现在可以告诉你的是我们确实有了一个计划
All I can tell you is we do have a plan.
是的  你们到丛林里去找炸药然后炸开一个舱门
Go into the jungle, get some dynamite, blow open a hatch,
然后就可以让大家躲在里面了
and then you hide everyone inside.
天知道那些炸药在那儿多久了
God knows how long that dynamite has been out there.
所以如果你不想被炸飞的话
So, unless you want to blow up,
就让我一起去
I'm coming with you.
-祝你好运  -你也一样
-Good luck.  -Same to you.
马上会再见面的
See you soon.
扶正了
Keep it straight.
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：e0yue
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
好了  推  推
Go, go!
再见了  Vincent
Bye, Vincent.
Claire  大家都准备走了
Claire. Everybody's leaving.
是的  我哪儿也不能去  行么?
Well, I can't go anywhere, all right?
我有个孩子  我太累了
I've got the baby and I'm... I'm so tired.
我不能带着他
I can't... can't carry him.
现在他又尿湿了
And now he's wet
边上又到处是沙子  我没有别的尿布了
and there's sand everywhere. I don't have anymore nappies.
你怎么不让我帮忙?
Why don't you let me help?
不  听着  没人和我说过这该怎么办
No, look, nobody ever taught me how to do this. Okay?
Claire  会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
为什么大家都对我这么说?
Why do people keep telling me that?
他们难道也有孩子么?
Are they the ones with the baby?
我们得在太阳下山前赶到那儿
We've got to get there before sundown.
一旦你们到了洞里  就呆在那儿
Once you reach the caves, stay there.
其他的人会马上到的
The rest of us will be right behind you.
听着  我知道Jack把它们给你了
I know Jack gave 'em to you.
我现在就要一把  我想保护Claire
I want one right now. I have to protect Claire.
Rousseau说那些人在黄昏的时候才会来
Rousseau said the others won't be here till night.
Rousseau是可以相信  但万一他们提前来了呢...
She's certifiable. What if they show up before?
上次你用枪的时候...
Last time you had a sidearm...
我杀了一个杀人犯  我帮了大家
I killed a murderer. I did us a favor.
Charlie  你控制不了你的情绪  那些枪由我来处理
You're emotionally involved. Let me handle the weapons.
你不会永远都在这里  你保护不了Claire  听着  我要一把枪
You're not here all the time. You can't protect her. I need a gun.
如果你真的想要帮Claire
If you want to help Claire
就帮她去整理东西  帮她把孩子带去山洞那里
get her packed, carry her child to the caves.
那才是她需要的
That's what she needs.
像这样的事怎么会发生的?
How exactly does something like this happen?
你和我在同在这个岛上  不是么?
Are you on the same island as I am?
这个解释还算不错
I guess that explains it.
停下  停下  等等  停下  等等
Hold on, wait... Hold, wait.
我们在哪儿  在几英里深的岛内陆?
What are we, a couple miles inland?
海啸是有可能把这东西刮过来的  是么?
A tsunami probably swept it here. Huh? Right?
你去哪儿?
Hey.Hey, where are you going?
炸药就在船体里
The explosives are in the hold of the ship.
Rousseau  等等
Rousseau, wait.
你吩咐的我都做了
I did what you asked.
你需要的是炸药  你不需要我了
You need dynamite. You don't need me.
让她去吧  Jack
Let her go, Jack.
谁带我们回去?
Who's gonna lead us back?
我会带大家回去的
I'll lead us back.
混蛋
Damn it.
你听她说了吧  炸药就在船体里面  我们走吧
You heard her. Explosives are in the hold. Let's go.
等等  等等
Hold on.
我来这儿是告诉你们怎样处理炸药
I came here to tell you how to handle dynamite,
不是和你们去鬼船探险的
not explore a ghost ship.
-你认为我会去...  -好了  好的  就呆在这儿吧
-You think...  -Just... stay out here.
我也和Arnzt一起呆在外面
I'm gonna stay out here and hang with Arnzt.
是奴隶
Slaves.
这艘船一定是准备去一个采矿的殖民地的
This ship must have been en route to a mining colony.
可能是从非洲的东海岸莫桑比克起航的
Probably set off from the eastern coast of Africa.
Jack  John  来一下
Jack. John. Over here.
然后我的第三个妻子  她说... 拿去  她说
and then my third wife, she says, get this,
我不是被你雇来的
"I didn't sign up for this."
现在你告诉我  这到底是什么意思?
You tell me, what the hell is that even supposed to mean?
我打扰你了么?
What, am I boring you?
呃?
Huh?
你知道么?  我...  我很抱歉
You know what? I'm sorry.
我...我很抱歉  我不够酷
I'm sorry that I'm not cool enough
我不能成为你们快乐的小冒险队的一员
to be part of your merry little band of adventurers.
什么?
What?
一看到这个小团体我就能知道  我是教高中的  伙计
I know a clique when I see it. I teach high school, pally!
你们这帮人认为你们是在这个岛上唯一做着有价值的事的人
You know, you people think you're the only ones on this island doing anything of value.
坠机事故中还有其他的40个幸存者
There were 40 other survivors of this plane crash,
并且我们也是一份子
and we are all people too.
好的
Okay.
你知道么?  我能把它打开一旦...
You know what,I can probably get it open if I just...
不  不  我们得搬出去
No. We should take it outside.
为什么? 我们甚至不知道...
Why? You don't even know if this...
我们不会用镐去撬开一个写有"炸药"的板条箱的  Kate
You're not prying open a crate that says "Explosives" with a pickax.
我同意Jack说的
Yeah, I agree with Jack.
我们把它搬出去  在外面打开
Take it outside, open it there.
好吧
Okay.
我来搬
I got it.
去带路好么?
You mind showing us the way?
那也不是些十几岁的青少年
It's not just the teenagers.
体育老师  你认为他们在咖啡馆里会让我和他们一起坐么?
The gym teachers,you think they let me sit with them in the cafeteria?
不  他们不会
No. They do not.
伙计  那全是你想出来的
This is all in your head.
真的么? 那么你向我解释一下
Really? You explain to me
为什么Kate用来做掩蔽处的飞机残骸是最好的?
why Kategets the best pieces of wreckage for her shelter?
还有那个韩国人...
And the Korean guy.
他抓的鱼分给了这个岛上的每一个人了么?
Does he catch fish for everybody on the island?
不  他没有  他没有
No. He does not. He doesn't.
并且在这儿的一些人明显瘦了不少
And some of us have actually lost weight while we were here.
现在你能告诉我你把食物都藏在哪儿了么?
You mind telling me where you're hiding the carbs?
因为我想不通...
'Cause I can't figure...
你们这些人到底在做什么?
What the hell are you people doing?
等等  等下  停  就停在那儿
Wait, wait. Stop. Stop right where you are.
好了  我要你们仔细慢慢放下箱子  仔细一点
Put that down carefully. Put it down carefully.
放得...轻一点  轻一点  混蛋
Put it gently...Gently. Damn it!
仔细一点  轻轻的  轻轻的
Carefully, gently. Gently.
好了  马上离开那儿  离远一点
Get outta there. Get away from it. Come on.
快点  走开  离它远点
Get out. Move away from it.
-到底这是...  -嘘  安静点
-What the hell is your...?  -Shh. Be quiet.
你们有人知道么
Do any of you have any idea
给黄色炸药加上90度的热度会怎样?
what happens to dynamite in 90-plus degree heat?
恩? 你们知道么?
Huh? Do you know?
有人知道么?
Any of you?
它会化成硝化甘油
It sweats nitroglycerin.
你干吗? 我说过让你走近了么?
What are you doing? Did I ask you to come closer?
黄色炸药...
Dynamite...
是用黏土固定的硝化甘油
is nitroglycerine stabilized by clay.
硝化甘油是人们所知道的最危险最不稳定的炸药
Nitroglycerine is the most dangerous and unstable explosive known to man.
Kate  把你的衬衣给我
Hey Kate, gimme your shirt.
快  公主  把你的衬衣给我  我要把炸药包起来
Now. Princess, give me your shirt. I need to wrap the dynamite.
把它丢给我就好了  小心点
Just throw it to me, right here. Just be careful.
拜托  快点
Come on, hurry up.
好了 很好 现在后退 后退 后退
Okay, good. Now back up. Back up.
离我远点
Get outta my way.
你们有人听说过发明硝化甘油的那个人么?
Any of you ever hear about the guy who invented nitroglycerin?
也许没有  因为他把自己的脸给炸了
Probably not, because he blew his freaking face off.
他的实验室助手进去后
His lab assistant came into the room,
看见他的导师引爆了炸药
saw that his mentor had detonated,
说道"恩 我想这东西很管用"
and he said: "Huh. I guess this stuff does work."
好了 我们拿了够用的就好
We're not gonna take more of this stuff than we need,
因为硝化甘油真的是很不稳定
because nitroglycerine is extremely temperamental.
那么我们就...
So we just...
伙计
Dude.
先生你的包是没人看管的
Sir, your bag was unattended.
-我可以走了么?  -可以了 先生
-Am I free to go?  -Yes, sir.
我要赶飞机
I have a plane to catch.
你能帮我拿一下纸巾么  朋友?
Could you hand me a paper towel there, bud?
一张纸巾  这个坏了
Uh, paper towel, this one's broken.
你不懂英语  对不起
Oh. You don't speak English. Sorry.
就是这张纸巾了
什么
我是为...
Paik先生工作的
你的岳父 也就是你的老板
你一直在跟踪我?
是的
我知道你打算逃跑
但你要把那块表...
带给Paik先生在加利福尼亚的朋友
如果你做了其他的事...
任何事
你就会失去她
你没有自由
你以前从没有过...
将来也不会有
爸爸  看
Dad, look!
这么大的一个地方怎么会没有人发现过?
How does a place this big never get discovered?
我不知道
Don't know.
但是你能在那儿建一个海滩度假别墅
But you could build yourself one hell of a beach resort right over there.
好吧 你去建你的吧
Yeah, you build your resort.
我很开心能和这里永别
I'm happy to say goodbye to this place forever.
其他人怎么样了? 他们还好吧?
What about everybody else? Think they'll be okay?
希望他们能安全吧  伙计
I hope so, buddy.
至少在我们叫来救援之前
At least until we can get 'em some help.
你在唱Bob Marley的歌?
Singing Bob Marley?
不是
No.
怎么了? 你喜欢听Bob Marley?
Why? You like Bob Marley?
伙计  有谁不喜欢Bob Marley?
Man, who doesn't like Bob Marley?
混蛋
Damn it!
那些东西你都要么?
Do you really need all that?
是的
Yeah. I do.
为什么你要带这么多?
Why do you have to bring so much?
你不是要带我们远足么?
Don't you have a hike to lead?
我没事
I'm fine.
这些都是你哥哥的东西
These belonged to your brother.
我需要这些东西
I need these things.
我不能抛下它们
I can't just leave them.
我们在做什么?
What are we doing?
躲起来?
Hiding?
好像他们找不到我们似的
As if they won't find us.
这只是...
It's just...
负担太重了
It's too much.
这太重了
如果我帮你承担一点的话就不会太困难了
It won't be too much if I carry it for you.
好了  快点吧
Now come on.
我要带你们远足
I have a hike to lead.
你还好吧?
You okay?
真是一团糟
That was messed up.
他刚刚...
He just...
被炸死了...
...exploded...
就在我们眼前
...in front of us.
他只是想帮我们
He was just trying to help.
-都怪我来了  -什么?
-This is because I came.  -What?
我...
I'm...
是一个扫把星
...kind of bad luck.
那只是一个意外
It was an accident.
一个意外
An accident.
Locke
我们得好好想想
We should think about this.
好吧
All right.
也许这不是最好的办法
Maybe this isn't the best way.
这是唯一的方法  Jack
It's the only way, Jack.
炸开那个舱门我们需要多少炸药?
How many do we need to blow the hatch?
炸开舱门盖要用两根
Two should take care of the hinge.
-带三根保险一点  -保险?
-Three to be safe.  -Safe.
我把干燥的那些拿掉了  以减少我们运输途中的危险
I'm removing the driest pieces to minimize our risk transporting it.
你玩过"军事行动"这个游戏么?
You ever play Operation?
当然  别碰到两头
Sure. "Don't touch the sides."
我...
I...
我总是碰到...
I always got nailed...
胳膊肘上
on the funny bone.
滋
Bzzzz!
你喜欢玩游戏是么 John?
You like to play games, John?
绝对喜欢
Absolutely.
好了
Okay.
我知道我们赶着逃去山洞那里
I know we're in a rush to escape to the caves,
所以我解决了这小家伙的运输问题
so I've solved the Turnip-Head transport issue.
这是飞机上的毯子
This is, uh, just a blanket from the plane.
然后我用了这个木头这样穿过这个竹子
And then, this piece of wood here that goes through this bamboo.
就是这个了
Here you go.
一个"bjorn"
It's a bjorn.
一个"bjorn"?
A bjorn?
Bjorn 是荷兰语的...襁褓的意思
bjorn. It's Dutch for, uh, baby carrier.
-谢谢  -不客气
-Yeah. Thanks.  -Well, that's okay.
-谢谢  -哦 谢谢
-Thank you.  -Thanks.
没事儿
That's okay.
把他放这儿
Let's put him there.
-Sayid 他在那儿?  -Rousseau 怎么...
-Sayid! Where is he?  -What...?
-Sayid 他在哪儿?  -他已经走了
-Sayid, where is he?  -He already left.
-我要马上见到他  -Jack和Kate...
-I need him now!  -Jack and Kate?
来不及了  Sayid在哪儿?
There's no time! Where is Sayid?
好了  冷静点  好么?  我把他找来
All right, just calm down. I'll get him for you.
-呆在这儿  好么?  -好的
-Stay here, all right?  -Okay.
那边发生了什么事?
What happened out there?
他叫什么名字?
What is his name?
我还没给他取名
Oh, I haven't named him yet.
我可以抱抱他么?
May I hold him?
你为什么要找Sayid?
Um, why do you need Sayid?
你不肯让我抱他
You don't want me to hold him?
不  我刚喂饱他  我想那样不好 是吧?
No, I just fed him. I don't think it's a good idea. Okay?
拜托
Please!
我什么时候弄的?
When did I do that?
我为什么要抓伤你?
Why did I scratch you?
怎么了?
What's going on?
呃...我去洛杉矶的飞机几小时后就要起飞了
Uh...My flight. L, uh...My flight to LA leaves in a couple of hours,
所以现在得走了 你知道么? 呃...
so you gotta get moving, you know? Uh...
你路上要再带一包海洛因么?
You wanna do one more bump for the road?
我们昨晚都吸完了  我有几瓶香槟
We did it all last night. I got some champagne.
你一定还留着几包
You gotta have some left.
不  全没了
Nope. It's done.
我下次来悉尼我会再来找你的  好么?
I'll look you up next time I'm in Sydney, okay.
我会  送你一张我亲笔签名的CD
I'll, uh, send you an autographed copy of, uh, my CD,
然后你就能随时随刻听我的歌了
then you can listen when you want.
我不想要你那什么混蛋乐队的烂CD
I don't want your crap CD from your crap band.
昨晚在酒吧里你说你是我们的歌迷
Last night in the bar, you said you were a fan.
好吧  我是一个狂热的歌迷
Fine. I'm a huge fan.
驱动器乐队是最好的混蛋乐队
Drive Thru is the best damn band ever.
现在  给我一包海洛因  我知道你有
Now just gimme a bump, 'cause I know you got some.
主动轴
Shaft.
是主动轴乐队
Drive Shaft.
你手里的是什么?
What's that in your hand?
没什么
Nothing.
-你瞒着我?  -我瞒着你?  不  没有
-Holding out on me?  -I'm not holding out.
给我
Give it to me.
给你什么? 我什么都没拿
What? I'm not holding.
快给我
Get off!
起来
Get up!
松手  松手
Let it go. Let it go!
-你怎么了  疯了么?  -松手
-What are you, crazy?  -Let it go!
-下去  -松手
-Get off!  -Let it go!
滚开
Get off!
-从我身上滚开
-Get off me!
你这个可怜虫
You're pathetic.
You're pathetic!
Sayid  Sayid
Rousseau在海滩那儿  她要见你
Rousseau's on the beach. She needs you.
-Rousseau? 怎么了?  -我不知道
-Rousseau? What for?  -I don't know.
救命  救命  来人啊
Help! Help!
救命  来人啊  救命
Help! Someone! Help!
怎么了?
What happened?
她的头
Her head.
他还好么?
Is he all right?
她抢走了我的孩子?
Did she take my baby?
她抢走了我的孩子是么?
她往哪儿去了?
Which way did she go?
我不知道
I don't know!
她抢走了我的孩子
She took my baby!
全怪你  是你把他带到我们营地来的
This is your fault! You brought her into the camp!
当初如果你给我一把抢的话...
If you had given me a gun...
不准再打我了
Do not hit me again.
你是想浪费时间来抱怨么
You want to waste time assigning blame?
这些时间足够让我们去找她了
There's plenty to go around.
她先走了  如果我们现在就去  还能赶上她
She has a head start. If we leave now, we can catch her.
我们怎么能追上她?
How we gonna do that?
因为我知道她往哪儿去了
Because I know where she's going.
不  不要...我要找回我的孩子
Please now... I want my baby.
你可以把炸药全部放我包里
I can carry all the sticks in my pack.
中间隔离的东西越多越好
The more insulation we stuff in, the better.
我想我们应该分开来拿
I think we should split 'em up.
什么?
What?
把它们放一起是很不明智的  我们还是分开带吧
It's not smart to keep it all together, so we split 'em up.
如果我们要3根来炸开舱门盖的话  我们就要带上6根炸药
If we need three sticks to blow the hinge, then we should bring six.
三个三个分开拿
Three and three.
以防万一我们其中一人...
A fail-safe. In case one of us...
那就你和我吧
You and me then.
不  我要带一包
No. I'm taking one.
这不可能  不行
Not gonna happen.
-我来这儿就是为了这个  -那么你就是白来了
-This is why I came.  -You wasted a trip.
我必须要这么做
I need to do this.
Kate  没人欠别人什么
Kate, no one owes anyone anything.
-我要带一包  -没得说了
-I'm carrying one.  -We're done.
-这不是由你来定的  -Kate 这就是由我来定的
-This is not your decision.  -It is.
我们抽签吧
We'll draw straws.
他们就要来了
They're coming...
我们没时间来决定由谁来冒这个险了  那么...
We don't have time to argue about who risks their life, so.
我们就让命运来决定吧
we let fate decide.
我同意
Works for me.
你呢?  也想带点炸药么?
What about you? You wanna carry some dynamite?
你的身上...
You got some...
Arnzt的...
Arnzt on you.
谁抽到短的就由谁来背炸药
Short sticks carry the packs.
就是你和我了  Kate
Looks like it's you and me, Kate.
这东西是用来干嘛的?
So, what's this stuff even do?
这个是发报机  向别人发送求救信号的
Well, the transmitter sends out an SOS in case someone's listening.
并且在这片海域里有什么动静的话
And if there's anything out there,
我们都可以在这个雷达屏幕里看到
we'll see it on this radar screen here.
开始吧
Here we go.
拜托
Come on.
来人救我们
Someone, find us.
这些都是大家写的信息
Those are messages everybody wrote.
当然是
Sure are.
他们是隐私的东西
They're private.
是的
Yep.
我从来没注意到Tracy是这么想念她在弗雷斯诺的丈夫和孩子们
I for one never knew how much Tracey missed her hubby and two kids back in Fresno.
但是她晚上还是睡在Scott身边取暖
Yet she's sleeping next to good ol' Scott to keep her warm at night.
那是Steve Scott死了
That's Steve. Scott's dead.
随便了  这旅途会很漫长  我们得找东西来开心开心
Whatever. Long ride, Kazoo. We gotta keep ourselves entertained.
Hugo究竟是谁  他怎么会留给他妈妈1亿6千万美元?
Who the hell is Hugo and how's he got a hundred and sixty million dollars to leave to his mom?
如果我读你的你会怎么想?
How'd you like it if I read yours?
你读不到我的  因为我没写过
You can't 'cause I didn't write one.
为什么不写?
Why not?
因为我唯一写过的一封信是给我要去杀的那个人的
'Cause the only letter I ever wrote is to the man I'm gonna kill.
你为什么要杀他?
Why you gonna kill him?
因为我必须这么做
'Cause I need to.
就是因为
Because.
你在开什么玩笑?
Are you bloody joking?
她为什么会去黑烟那儿?
Why would she go for the black smoke?
那儿不就是"其他人"应该在的地方么?
Isn't that where the others are?
她去那儿就是为了找那些人
The others are why she would go there.
Rousseau告诉我们16年前她的孩子被抢了的当天她就看到了黑烟
Rousseau told us she saw black smoke the day her own child was taken 16 years ago.
他们抢走了她的孩子
They took something from her.
现在她相信
And now she believes...
她有他们想要的东西
she has something they want.
她准备拿孩子做交换?
She's making a trade?
我相信她是这么想的
I believe she is. Yes.
太疯狂了  她脑子有病
That's insane. She's insane.
别指责她的所做所为
Don't apply reason to her actions.
她是一个失去孩子的母亲...就像Claire一样
She's a mother who lost her child. Just like Claire.
这次去不是为了报仇
This isn't about revenge.
别太自私
Don't make it personal.
我也要去
I'm coming with you.
这不行  Claire
That's not a good idea.
那是我的孩子  好么?  是我让她抢走的
This is my baby, okay. I let her take him.
-Claire 听着...  -别告诉我我该怎么做 可以么?
-Claire, listen.  -Don't tell me what to do!
冷静点
Calm down.
我也要和你们一起去
I am coming with you.
这全怪我 我要去 好么? 你阻止不了我的
This is my fault and I'm coming and you can't stop me!
-好了好了  -我也要去
-It's fine, all right. It's all right.  -I'm supposed to raise him.
把他带回来  Charlie
Get him back, Charlie.
把Aaron带回来
Get Aaron back.
Aaron?
求你把他带回来  求你了
Please. Get him back. Please.
Claire  我会把他带回来的  我保证
Claire, I will get him back. Promise.
你想吃点什么么?
Hey, you want something to eat?
我想你是不要了
I guess that's a "no" then.
如果你是在为Vincent担心  它会没事的  伙计
If you're worried about Vincent, he's gonna be okay, man.
狗坐飞机都是要进行李舱的
Dogs fly in the luggage compartment all the time.
好吧
All right.
我去打个电话
I gotta call work.
呆在这儿
Right over there.
哪儿都别去  好么?
Don't go anywhere, okay?
不  我住在小公寓住宅里
No, I live in a studio apartment.
我得在早上5点钟之前赶去工作
I gotta be out the door in the morning for work by 5am.
谁来照看他?
Who's gonna watch him?
他怎么去学校? 他放学后怎么办?
How's he getting to school? What about after?
我不能这么做  妈
I can't do this, Ma.
你知道  我...
You know, I was...
听着  我在想
Listen, I was thinking, um...
我在想也许你能照看一下他
I was thinking maybe you could take him.
妈  如果这是钱的问题的话 我...
But Ma, if it's a question of money, I...
然么我该拿他怎么办?
What am I supposed to do with him?
他不应该是我的
He's not supposed to be mine.
这可不是当初就想好的
This was never part of the plan.
好吧  我...
Yeah, I...
伙计
Hey, man.
-我在  呃...  -我要新电池
-I was, uh...  -I need new batteries.
要试一下么?
You wanna try?
-什么?  -来吧 过来
-What?  -Come on, come here.
你来试着驾驶一会儿
You drive for awhile.
-真的么?  -是啊
-Really?  -Absolutely.
好的  听着  舵是船最重要的部分
Okay, now. Look.The most important part of this boat is the rudder.
我告诉你怎么掌舵
It's how you steer.
慢慢地转动  别太用力  好么?
You turn it gradually. Nothing sharp, okay?
往这儿推
Push it this way.
我们往哪儿走?
Where are we going?
看
Look.
我们大约是往北方或东北方向移动
So we're going approximately north by northeast.
这样我们就会有希望驶上海洋航线...
So hopefully that puts us into a shipping lane.
或是看到陆地之类的
Or we hit some land.
我该怎么找准方向?
What do I aim for?
看到地平线那儿的云了么?
See that cloud on the horizon?
恩
Yeah.
你就朝那儿走吧
You aim for that.
-好的  -我知道了
-Okay.  -Got it.
为什么你和我妈妈不住在一起呢?
How come you and my mom didn't stay together?
我们尝试过了
We tried.
但没有用  我们的生活  我们的爱好...
It just didn't work out. So our lives, our interests
完全是不同路的
just went in different directions.
那为什么我从没见到过你?
How come I never saw you?
因为你妈妈不想让我见你
'Cause your mom didn't want me to.
她认为她做的一切都是为你好
She did what she thought was best.
她错了
She was wrong.
舵
Rudder.
舵掉了
We lost the rudder.
舵  舵
Rudder. Rudder.
它沉下去了  我们会丢了舵
We're losing it! It's sinking!
把船停下
Stop the boat.
Stop the boat!
把帆收起来
Just pull the sail down.
爸爸
Dad!
Sawyer
Sawyer  把绳子给我
Sawyer! Give me the rope. Throw it.
-Sawyer  -它在下沉
-Sawyer!  -It's sinking.
我够不到
I can't reach it.
把它拴在舵板上  我们会把你拉回来的
Tie it around the rudder and we'll pull you in!
好的
Okay.
Michael.
加油  伙计
Come on, buddy.
你救了我们的命  伙计
You just saved our ass, buddy.
这是你的衬衣  在你被晒伤前你最好穿上
Here's your shirt. You should put that back on before you burn.
-抱歉  -恩 没事...
-Sorry.  -Yeah, well...
中签很幸运
It's the luck of the draw.
太阳大约90分钟后下山
Sun sets in 90 minutes, give or take.
我们要回舱门那儿就得快点动身了
If we want to get back to the hatch, we have to hustle.
好的  我们这么做
Okay, this is how we do this.
我带路  Kate  你跟着我
I'll lead. Kate, you're right behind me.
然后是Hurley  John  你最后
Then Hurley. John, you bring up the rear.
如果你看见我走错路了...
If you see me heading the wrong way...
我们应该错开队形
We should stagger our formation.
相互之间保持一定的安全距离
Keep a safe distance from each other.
好的  我们错开走
All right. We stagger.
如果有人听见什么或是看到什么...
If anyone hears anything or sees anything...
像是吃人的安全系统之类的?
Like the security system that eats people?
就像那个
Yeah. Like that.
你们两个卸下背包放到地上马上跑  懂了么?
You two, you take your packs off, you put 'em down and you run. You got it?
-知道了  -是的 长官
-Got it.  -Yes, sir.
好的  我们走吧
Okay. Let's do this.
他死得很勇敢
He died bravely.
什么?
What?
你的哥哥
Your brother.
是的
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
你认为这些事...
Do you think all this...
我们所经历的这些...
...all we've been through...?
你认为是我们所受的惩罚么?
Do you think we're being punished?
对于什么的惩罚?
Punished for what?
我们以前的所做所为
Things we did before.
我们隐瞒的秘密
The secrets we kept.
我们说的谎言
The lies we told.
你认为是谁在惩罚我们?
Who do you think is punishing us?
命运
Fate.
没人在惩罚我们
No one's punishing us.
这世上没有命运这回事
No such thing as fate.
-你还好吧?  -我没事 继续走吧
-Are you okay?  -I'm fine. Keep going.
天色暗下来了
We're losing the light.
-尽量跟上  -我来了
-Try to keep up.  -I'm coming.
Sayid
在这儿
Over here.
Sayid?
你太累了  我们休息一下
You can barely breathe. We're going to rest.
休息?  她现在就在那儿...
Rest? She's out there right now.
还差很远  你会受不了的
In another mile, you're going to collapse.
我们得休息一下
We're going to take a break.
Boone就是在这儿摔下来的么?
Is this where Boone fell?
这架飞机本来是在上面的
The plane was up there.
它是从哪儿来的?
Where did it come from?
根据里面的地图来看  是从尼日利亚来的
Based on the maps inside, Nigeria.
上面有人么?
Anyone onboard?
两个穿的像牧师的人
Two men, dressed as priests.
-牧师?  -伪装成牧师的毒贩
-Priests?  -Drug runners in disguise.
满飞机都是海洛因
The plane was loaded with heroin.
知道了...
All right.
我们该走了
Now we go.
伙计  你认为在那个舱门里面的是什么?
So, dude, what do you think's inside that hatch thing?
你认为那里面有什么?
What do you think's inside it?
像是一堆50年代的冷冻快餐什么的
Stacks of TV dinners from the fifties or something.
还有连着电缆的电视 手机 干净的袜子 香皂 还有类似三明治的东西
And TVs with cable. Some cell phones. Clean socks. Soap. Twinkies.
你知道  就当作是餐后的甜点吧
You know, for dessert after the TV dinners.
那种三明治可以保存8000年左右  伙计
Twinkies keep for, like, 8,000 years, man.
我也很喜欢那种三明治似的东西
I like Twinkies too.
好了  说真的  你认为里面有什么?
Come on, really. What do you think's inside?
希望
Hope.
我认为里面有我们的希望
I think hope's inside.
不管是谁  把这儿叫做"黑暗地域"的人...都是天才
Whoever named this place Dark Territory,genius.
是的  我看见了
Yeah. I saw it.
我们得快点离开这儿
We gotta get out of here.
Locke  你在干什么?
Locke! What are you doing?
Locke
Locke  Locke
Jack?
Jack
我的天那  Locke
Oh, my God. Locke!
我需要炸弹
I need the dynamite!
不  它们在我的包里
No, no. It's in my pack.
快去拿来  快去
Go get it! Hurry! Go!
没事的  John  你会没事的
John. John, just hold on.
-让我去吧  -什么?
-Just let me go.  -What?
-我会没事的   -不
-I'll be all right.  -No!
放手吧  我不会有事的
-Let me go! I'll be all right.
好了  我拿到了
I got it! I got it!
小心打开
Be careful unwrapping it.
-扔下去  -不  会把我们炸飞的
-Now throw it in.  -No! Lt'll blow us up.
-快扔下去 快  -别这么做  Kate
-Do it! Hurry! I can't hold him.  -Don't do this.
扔下去
Throw it in.
快  Kate
Now, Kate!
你的妻子
Your wife...
是你的妻子帮你做的么?
wife made this for you?
Sun
她把它们的发音写出来了  恩?  这样你就能学英语了
She sounded it out, huh? So you can learn English.
我希望她也帮我做一份
Yeah, I wish she made one for me.
那么  这儿有些什么单词?
So, what words are in here?
英语单词  你会说哪些?
English words. What can you say?
右船舷
Starboard.
船尾
Aft.
向左转舵
Port.
航行
Uh... Sail.
吃
Uh...Eat.
很好  她帮你做的很好  希望你能了解你是多么幸运  伙计
Yeah, right. She did you well. I hope you know how lucky you are, man.
继续干活?
Back in business?
这是你的
Oh, hey, it's yours.
你
You.
什么?
What?
你
You.
谢谢...你 谢谢
Um...Thank... you. Thanks.
我给你煮了点茶
I made you some tea.
我很好
I'm fine.
谢谢
Thanks.
Aaron这个名字很好听  它代表了什么?
Aaron is a beautiful name. What does it mean?
我不知道Aaron代表了什么
I don't know what Aaron means.
他们会把他带回来的
They will bring him back.
-别谈那个  -他们会的
-Don't say that.  -They will.
-你怎么可能知道?  -因为他说了他会的
-How do you know that?  -Because he said he would.
Charlie会把你孩子带回来的
Charlie will bring your baby back.
Charlie  等等
Charlie, wait!
Charlie
让我看看  让我看看
See. Let me see.
我在流血
It's bleeding.
使劲按住
We need to put pressure on it.
好的  使劲
Okay. Put pressure.
-哦  -垫上毛巾
-Ow!  -There.
-畜牲 她怎么...  -别松手 就像这样
-Animal! What is she...? Ow!  -Keep the pressure on, like this!
她在这儿16年了  她学会了怎样快速制造机关
She's been here for 16 years. She's learned how to set traps quickly.
好了  让我看看
Okay, let's have a look.
伤口太深了  血流了很多
It's too deep. It's bleeding too much.
你得回去
You have to go back.
不  我不回去  你得治好我
I'm not. You have to fix it.
我不是医生
I'm not a doctor.
你是军人  军人打仗时受伤了会怎么办?
You're a soldier! What do people do when they get wounded?
没拿回孩子我是不会回去的  Sayid
I'm not going back without that baby, Sayid.
别动
Don't move.
火药?
Gunpowder?
把毛巾拿开  头翘起来
Remove the towel, tilt your head back.
拿开毛巾
Remove the towel.
就是因为我打了你你才这样  是么?
This is because I hit you, isn't it?
这是不会太舒服的
This is not going to be pleasant.
-准备好了么?  -是的
-You ready?  -Yes.
1...2...3
One. Two. Three.
哦  天哪
Oh, man.
帮我把车备好
I need my car.
20分钟?
Twenty minutes?
听着  我不能错过飞机  明天是我妈的生日
Look, I can't miss my flight. My mom's birthday's tomorrow.
快点  快点  快点  快点  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on. Cool.
我们这儿有人要赶飞机
Some of us have a bloody flight to make.
抱歉 借过
Excuse me. Coming through.
抱歉  抱歉  抱歉
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
快  快
Come on. Come on.
不  不  不  不
No. No. No! No!
抱歉  抱歉  小心  借过
Excuse me. Excuse me. Look out! Excuse me.
抱歉  抱歉  小心  抱歉
Excuse me. Excuse me. Look out. Coming through.
能快点么?  我妈明天生日
Any way we can hurry that up? My mom's birthday's tomorrow.
或是今天  我不知道  我不想换另一架班机
Or... today. I don't know, I don't really get the whole time change thing,
我一定要上飞机
but I gotta make that flight.
我已经尽可能的快了  亲爱的
I am going as fast as the system will allow me, dear.
你的座位号是20G
You are confirmed for seat 20-G.
不过航空公司有规定  像你这种体积的人要买两张票
However, the airline has a policy that a man of your size must purchase two tickets.
什么? 我来的时候没买两张票啊
What? I didn't have to do that on the flight out here.
你要称一下你有多重么  亲爱的?
Am I going to have to weigh you, dear?
好了  无所谓了
Fine. Whatever.
我再买一张紧挨着的座位票
I'll buy the one next to it.
好的  两张票
Alrighty. Here's two together.
呃哦  呃哦什么?
"Uh-oh"? What "uh-oh"?
看来你的航班已经在海洋国际航班检录处开始检票登机了
It appears that your flight is already boarding in the international terminal.
这儿是国内航班登机处
This is the domestic terminal.
我认为你赶不上这趟飞机了  亲爱的
I don't think you're meant to make this flight, dear.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉  借光
Pardon me.
抱歉  不好意思
Excuse me. Sorry.
抱歉  抱歉  借光
Excuse me. Sorry. Excuse me.
抱歉  抱歉  借过一下
Excuse me! Coming through. Behind you.
小心  小心  小心  小心
Look out!
抱歉 抱歉
Excuse me. Excuse me.
抱歉  抱歉
不好意思
Sorry.
不好意思  很紧急  我只好插队了
Sorry,this is an emergency. I gotta...I gotta cut through.
抱歉  伙计  伙计
Excuse me. Dude. Dude.
-回去排队  -我要赶不上...不
-Back of the line.  -Let me go ahead. I'm gonna miss my...
-回去排队  -你不明白  这是...
-Back of the line.  -You don't understand. This is...
回去排队
Back of the line.
下一个
Next.
现在?  你现在就要把电脑拿出来么?
Now? You're taking the computer out now?
老伙计
Hey! Old guy!
我给你500美元  借我一下你的车好么
I'll give you 500 to borrow your scooter.
我刚做了臀部移位  我需要这东西
I just had a hip replacement. I need this.
好吧
Okay.
1600美元
Sixteen hundred bucks.
抱歉  抱歉
Excuse me. Excuse me.
借过
Whoa! Coming through!
小心   小心  小心
Look out. Look out, look out.
小心 抱歉 抱歉
Excuse me. Excuse me.
小心  注意  借过  小心
Look out.  Heads up. Coming through. Look out.
借过  借过  借过
Coming through. Coming through.
你好  抱歉
Konnichiwa. Excuse me.
小心  借过
Yeah, coming through.
小心  小心
Look out! Look out!
等一下  等一下  等等关门
Hey! Hold it! Hold the door! Hold the door!
等...等等关门
Hold... Hold the door!
我得上这架飞机
I gotta get on... this flight!
先生  登机口已经关闭了
Sir, the Jetway's closed.
求你了  我代表全世界的真爱和圣洁
Please. For the love of all that is good and holy in the world,
求你让我登机吧
let me on this plane.
好吧  等一下
All right, one second.
Hunter我是Jenna  这儿还有一个人
Hunter? This is Gina. We've got one more.
好的
Ta.
今天是你幸运的一天
This is your lucky day.
4  8  15  16  23  42
-4,8,15,16,23,42  -你在说什么?
-4,8,15,16,23,42  -You say something?
没什么
Nope.
我想我听见了"23"
I thought I heard 23.
那对你有什么意义么?
Does that mean something to you?
什么?
What?
那个数字"23"
That number? 23?
那个在澳大利亚收留过我的人
The guy who called the feds on me back in Australia
为了23000的赏金出卖了我
did it for a $23,000 reward.
对你有什么意义么?
Mean something to you?
没有
Nah.
只是一个数字
It's just a number.
我们得赶上去了
Better catch up.
快看不见他们了
I can barely see 'em.
我们不能离得这么近  Jack
We shouldn't be this close to each other, Jack.
如果爆炸了  就一起被炸吧
If we blow up, we blow up.
到底是怎么一回事  John?
What the hell was all that about back there?
什么怎么回事?
What was what about?
-在那儿你让我松手  -恩 是的
-You asked to let you go.  -That's right.
不  那东西正在把你往洞里拉
That thing was taking you down the hole.
-它不会伤害我的  -不 John 它会杀了你
-It wasn't gonna hurt me.  -It was gonna kill you.
我绝对表示怀疑
I seriously doubt that.
听着  我需要你...
Look, I need for you to...
我需要你向我解释你脑子里到底在想什么  John
I need for you to explain to me what the hell's going on inside your head.
我想知道你为什么认为那个东西不会...
I need to know why you believe that thing wasn't gonna...
我相信我正在被考验
I believe that I was being tested.
-考验?  -是的 考验
-Tested.  -Yeah. Tested.
我想这就是为什么我们有时不能互相了解的原因 Jack
I think that's why you and I don't see eye to eye sometimes, Jack.
因为你是一个相信科学的人
Because you're a man of science.
是的  那你呢?
Yeah. And what does that make you?
我?  我是一个相信命运的人
Me? Well, I'm a man of faith.
你真的以为这些都是一场事故么?
Do you really think all this is an accident?
我们  一帮陌生人  幸存了下来
That we, a group of strangers, survived.
其中很多人都只是受了很浅的一点伤
Many of us with just superficial injuries.
你以为我们是凑巧坠落到这个地方的么?
You think we crashed on this place by coincidence?
尤其是这个地方?
Especially this place.
我们被带到这儿来是有目的有原因的  我们大家都是
We were brought here for a purpose. For a reason. All of us.
我们每个人被带到这儿来都是有原因的
Each one of us was brought here for a reason.
被带来这里
Brought here?
是谁把我们带来这里的  John?
And who brought us here, John?
是这个岛把我们带到这儿来的
The island brought us here.
这不是一个寻常的地方  你也看见了  我知道你看见了
This is no ordinary place. You've seen that, I know you have.
这个岛也选择了你  Jack
The island chose you too, Jack.
这就是命运
It's destiny.
你和Boone也谈过命运了么  John?
Did you talk with Boone about destiny, John?
Boone是这个岛所要求的牺牲品
Boone was a sacrifice that the island demanded.
他在那架飞机里所发生的一切
What happened to him at that plane was a part of a chain of events
是把我们带到这儿来的一系列事件中的一件
that led us here,
这些事让我们走到了同一条路上
that led us down a path,
它们带我们到了今天  到了现在
that led you and me to this day, to right now.
这条路什么时候是个尽头  John?
And where's that path end, John?
尽头就在舱门那儿
The path ends at the hatch.
那个舱门  Jack
The hatch, Jack.
全部  发生的全部的事都是为了让我们能够打开舱门
All of it. All of it happened so we can open the hatch.
不  不  我们打开舱门是为了能幸存下来
No. No, we're opening the hatch so that we can survive.
幸存也是很有关系的  Jack
Survival is all relative, Jack.
我不相信命运
I don't believe in destiny.
不  你相信的
Yes, you do.
你只是还不了解罢了
You just don't know it yet.
我刚刚才打开过的
I turned it on a little while ago.
Sayid说过每小时打开一次
Sayid said every hour.
听着  我们已经离岛15英里远了  我们可能会在这儿呆上好几个星期
Look, we're 15 miles out. We could be here for weeks.
-如果电池用完了...  -他说了 每个小时
-If that battery runs out...  -The man said every hour.
5分钟  不能再长了
Five minutes. No more.
好  好
Aye, aye.
知道我喜欢你的哪一点么  Mike?
Know what I like about you, Mike?
你有圣人才有的耐心
You got the patience of a saint.
是么?  为什么你这么说?
Yeah? Why you say that?
我看到了他对你说话的方式
I've seen the way he talks to you.
他跑来跑去  做他愿做的事
The way he runs around, does whatever the hell he wants.
如果是我我早就会狠狠打他一顿了
I'd have shown him the back of my hand a long time ago.
你会的  是么?
You would, huh?
是的  你说对了
Hell of a lot cheaper than a shrink.
那是你父亲对待你的方式么?  狠狠打你一顿?
Is that what your father did to you? Show you the back of his hand?
我的爸爸没机会打我
My daddy never got a chance to beat me.
在我8岁的时候他开枪自杀了
Shot himself when I was eight.
这就是为什么你这么想死了?
That why you wanna die?
什么?
What?
自从你说你想上救生艇开始  我就想不通了
Since you told me you wanted on this raft, I couldn't figure it out.
为什么一个只知道关心自己的人会冒着生命危险去救其它人?
Why's a guy who only cares about himself wanna risk his life to save everyone else?
就我所知道的  这只有两个可能
Way I see it, there's only two choices.
你如果不是想成为一个英雄
You're either a hero,
就是想死了
or you wanna die.
我不是英雄  Mike
Well...I ain't no hero, Mike.
这代表了什么?
That what I think it is?
有东西在那边
Something's out there.
不好意思  先生  我们为残疾乘客特制的轮椅...
I'm sorry, sir, but the special wheelchair that we use for loading disabled passengers,
我们一下子找不到了
no one seems to know where it is right now,
在我们找到那张轮椅之前  我们无法让你登机
and unless we find it, I'm not sure we can get you on.
明天之前已经没有班次了
There's not another flight till tomorrow.
是的  我知道  先生  但是我真的没办法
I'm aware, but there's nothing I can do.
我能带着 Michelle  我们可以把他抬上去
Look, I can get Michelle. We can carry him on.
你不介意我们把你抬上去吧?
Mind if we carry you on?
不  那样很好
No, that would be fine.
就是这儿了
Here we go.
这儿是你的座位
Here's your seat.
我把你的包拿来  先生
I'll get your bags, sir.
如果有什么需要的  只要按这个钮就行了
If you need anything, press the "call" button.
好的
Okay.
把这些多余的炸药带远一点
Hugo, take these extra sticks back a couple hundred yards.
好的
Oh, okay.
知道了
Got it.
小心点
Be careful.
给我一个手电筒好么?
Can I have a flashlight?
因为  火把围着一根炸药
'Cause, uh, the torch around the dynamite thing,
对我来说太离奇了
not making sense to me.
Kate  你来牵导火索
Kate, you run the fuse.
Jack和我来装炸药
Jack and I will rig the charges.
好的
Okay.
那到底是什么?
What the hell is that?
看不见有脚印  没有什么痕迹
There's no footprints, no tracks.
就这些了? 这就是黑烟?
This is it? This is the black smoke?
他们在哪儿?
Where are they?
我不知道
I don't know.
Danielle?
马上
Right now!
冷静点
Calm down.
Danielle
我听到你在那儿了  出来吧
I can hear you. Come out.
求你了  他需要回到他母亲那儿
Please. He needs his mother.
他们不在这儿
They were not here.
Danielle  你得把孩子给我们
Danielle, you have to give us the baby.
我只是...
I just
想要回我的Alex
wanted my Alex back.
我以为...
I thought
如果我把这孩子交给他们...
if I gave them the baby...
好了
It's okay.
我知道
I know.
没事了
It's okay.
我拿稳了
I got him.
从来就没有什么"其他人"
There never were any others.
火是你自己点起来的
You started the fires yourself!
不  我听见他们的耳语声了
No. I heard them whispering.
你傻掉了
You're a nut job.
你根本什么也没听见
You heard nothing.
我听见他们说他们会来抢走孩子
I heard them say they were coming for the child.
"其他人"说他们会来抢走这男孩的
The others said they were coming for the boy.
你这个可怜虫
You're pathetic.
线
Wire.
抓住另一头
Hold that end.
现在是导火索了
Now the fuse.
我来吧
I'll do it.
-只能弄这么远了  -够远了
-That's as far as it goes.  -It's far enough.
我来点
I'll light it.
你们找个掩体躲好  我有足够的时间可以逃走
You take cover. There'll be enough burn time for me to get clear.
等一下
Wait. Just a sec.
那么刚才在那儿是怎么回事?
What was that about back there?
什么怎么回事?
What was what about?
把炸药放在你的包里
Putting the dynamite in your pack.
我做了一个判断与抉择
I made a judgment call.
我们是抽签的
We drew straws.
抱歉 但是我不会让像那样抽签来替我们做抉择的 Kate
I'm not gonna let drawing straws make decisions like that.
你没有权利这样
You had no right.
每个人都想让我来当领导者  直到我做出了他们不喜欢的决定
Everybody wants me to be a leader till I make a decision they don't like.
你想就这样一直在事后才来劝告我么  Kate?
You want to keep second guessing me?
那就是你的事了
That's your call.
你要知道一点
There's something you need to know.
如果我们这次活下来了  我们今晚就活下来了...
If we survive this, if we survive tonight...
我们还会有Locke的问题要解决
we're gonna have a Locke problem.
现在我想知道你是支持我的
And I have to know that you've got my back.
我支持你
I got your back.
准备好了么?
Are we ready?
等一下  等一下
Wait a sec. Wait a sec.
不  不  不  不
No, no, no.
停下
Stop!
停下  我们不能这么做
Stop, we can't do this.
停下  等等
Stop! Wait!
停下  我们不能这么做
Stop! We can't do this!
停下  停下  我们不能
Stop it! Stop it! We can't!
停下  别点  我们不能这么做
Stop, don't light it! We can't do this!
我们不能这么做  快停下
We can't do this! Stop!
停下  这些不是好数字  停下  快停下
We gotta stop it. The numbers are bad.
你在干什么?  你为什么那么做?
What are you doing? Why'd you do that?
等等  这些数字不是好数字
Wait! The numbers are bad!
这些数字不是好数字
The numbers are bad!
Hurley 停下 Hurley 你得赶快回来
Hurley, Stop!Hurley, You gotta get back.
你快回来  快回来
You gotta get back. You gotta get back.
越来越近了
It's closer.
-把信号枪给我  -等一下
-Give me the damn flare gun.  -Hold on.
越来越近了  告诉你  看看吧
It's closer. I'm telling you.
听着  我知道  好么?  我只有一发信号  就一发
I know, okay. I've got one flare. One flare.
什么?  好的  我知道了  你什么也没看到  好的
Okay. I know. You don't see anything.
你还等着能看见什么?
What the hell are you expecting?
万一你没看见呢  现在一片漆黑
In case you haven't noticed, it's dark.
那是什么?  是一艘船么?
What is it? Is it a ship?
我们不知道  小伙计  我们不知道
We don't know, little man.
右舷?  左舷?
Starboard? Port?
左舷  左舷
Uh... Port. Port.
好了  到底我该怎么做?
What the hell am I supposed to do?
你们两个停一下来看看这里好么?
Han. You and Chewie wanna slow down and talk to me?
我们得打信号枪了
We have to fire the flare.
我们不知道这是什么  任何东西都有可能
We don't know what it is. It could be anything. Junk.
一块在海上漂的舢板  我们甚至不知道Sayid的雷达管不管用
We don't know if Sayid's radar works.
你看见过那家伙修的东西失灵过么?
He ever fix something that don't?
它走远了
It's moving away.
漂浮着的舢板知道改变航线  恩?
Junk knows how to steer?
我们在动  这不代表...
We're moving. It doesn't mean...
听着  你是把信号枪给我
Are you gonna give me the damn gun
还是让我来抢?
or am I gonna have to take it?
你能怎么样  向我开枪?
What're you gonna do? Shoot me?
快消失了
It's almost gone!
快点了
Come on!
拜托  老天...
Please, God!
回来了
It's coming back!
我们在一个岛上呆了快一个月了  伙计
We've been on an island for a month, man.
飞机坠毁  恩?  呃  到底怎么回事?
Plane crash, huh? Well, how about that!
我们在一个岛上 呃 815航班 嘿 我们这是在哪儿?
We were on an island... flight 815... Hey, where are we?
好在我们找到了你们
Hey, it's a good thing we found you!
我们幸存了  并且  还有一群人和...
We survived, and there's a whole group of people on the island.
你们很了不起啊
Well, ain't that something.
是的
Yeah.
唯一的问题是  我们得把这孩子带走
Only, the thing is, we're gonna have to take the boy.
什么? 你说什么?
What? What'd you say?
这个男孩  我们得把他带走
The boy. We're gonna have to take him.
到底是怎么回事?
Hey, what the hell's going on here?
你们是什么人?
Who are you people?
把孩子给我们
Just give us the boy.
我不会给你们任何人的
I'm not giving you anybody.
那好吧
Well, all right then.
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad!
-不  Walt  不  -爸爸  爸爸
-No! Walt, no! -Dad! Dad!
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报 ====